D. Pavani Shrinija (1) Featured

Front end Developer seeking role in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Java, node JS, Spring MVC, Spring Boot, Rest API, Soap, JSON, HTML, CSS, JavaScript.



Current Designation: Front End Developer Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Accenture Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Visakhapatnam Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Hyderabad, Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Application Developer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Support, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Java, reactJS, nodeJS, Spring MVC, Spring

Boot, Rest API, Soap, JSON, HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

I have completed 2 years as a Front end Developer at Accenture I worked as a Developer in a project under Agile Methodology I have good knowledge and experience in Java, Spring MVC, JavaScript, Angular JS, Angular 7, HTML,CSS,JSP,JSON,mySql,restful and Soap webservices

Work Experience

Accenture as Front end developer Oct 2018 to Sep 2020

I have been working as a Front end developer at Accenture since the last 2 days. I developed user friendly and single page applications using all the latest technologies such as JavaScript,HTML,CSS, Spring MVC, Angular JS,JSP,mySql. I worked under a project in Agile methodologies

Accenture as Front End Developer Oct 2018 to Till Date

I worked as a Front end Developer at Accenture since the last 2 years. I developed user friendly and single page

applications using all the latest technologies such as JavaScript, HTML CSS Angular JS Spring MVC JSP mySql .I have a good knowledge on nodeJS and reactJS as well as Agile methodologies.

Accenture as Front End Developer Oct 2018 to Sep 2020

Project Experience

Description & Role

- 1. Worked under development of dynamic websites and single page applications using all the latest technologies (Java, Spring MVC, JavaScript, HTML, Angular7, AngularJS, mySql, JSP, nodeJs, reactJS, Jquery) and developed user friendly applications.
- 2. Collaborated with other developers on Designing, Developing, Testing and implementing new JSP Pages, HTML Pages.
- 3. Participated in Weekly Team Meetings, Scrum Calls and provided updates on the progress.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Gandhi Institute of Technology and Management, Visakhapatnam in 2018

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
JAVA	
Reactjs, nodejs	
SPRING MVC	
spring boot	
REST API	
Soap,JSON	
HTML,CSS	
JavaScript	
Angular7	
JQUERY	
JSP	
MySQL	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Telugu				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time